<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kool Kotlin</string>
    <string name="app_start">AUB - Mobile Development</string>
    <string name="con_dec">App Logo</string>
    <string name="add_button">+</string>


    <string name="add_title">Title :</string>
    <string name="add_time">Time :</string>
    <string name="add_type">Type :</string>
    <string name="add_style">Style :</string>
    <string name="add_pic">Picture :</string>
    <string name="add_vid">Video Link :</string>
    <string name="upload_pic">Upload</string>
    <string name="add_recipe">Add Recipe</string>
    <string name="pic">Null</string>

    <string name="test_title">Homemade Spicy Kung Pao Chicken Noodles</string>
    <string name="time_test">Time : 45 minutes</string>
    <string name="type_test">Type : Italian</string>
    <string name="style_test">Style : Pasta</string>
    <string name="test_ingredients">Ingredients</string>
    <string name="test_instruction">Instructions:</string>
    <string name="test_ingredients_details">Chicken broth, Light soy, Dark Soy Sauce, Chinese wine, Chinese black vinegar, Sichuan (or Szechuan) pepper, sugar, cornstarch, cooking oil,
garlic, ginger, red bell pepper, green bell pepper, dried chilies, sesame oil, roasted/unsalted peanuts.</string>

    <string name="test_instruction_details">1 -Combine all ingredients for the chicken in a shallow bowl; cover and marinate for 10 minutes (if time allows).\n2- Whisk sauce ingredients together until sugar dissolves; set aside.
\n3- Heat a large skillet, pan or wok over high heat. \n4- Add 2 tablespoons of cooking oil, allow to heat up, then add marinated chicken. Fry chicken for 3-4 minutes while occasionally stirring, until edges are browned. Remove from heat and set aside.
Add remaining cooking oil into the same pan/wok. Stir in garlic, ginger, chili diced peppers (capsicums) and Sichuan peppercorns and stir fry for 1 minute.
\n5- Give the prepared sauce a mix, then pour it into the pan and bring it to a boil while stirring.
\n6- Once it begins to thicken slightly, add chicken back into the pan/wok and mix all of the ingredients through the sauce until the chicken is evenly coated and sauce has thickened, (about 2 minutes).
\n7- Stir in green onions, peanuts and sesame oil. Toss well and continue to cook for a further 2 minutes to infuse all of the flavours together.
\n8- Serve immediately with steamed/cooked rice or fried rice!</string>

    <string name="test_notes">Notes:</string>
    <string name="test_notes_details">*Our kung pao sauce is not sweet for most of our readers and balances out the heat or spice-level. However, start with 1 teaspoon if you are hesitant or omit the sugar completely.
</string>

    <string name="watch">Watch Video Here!!</string>

    <string name="rate">Like it?</string>
    <string name="comment_title">Comments: (We value your input to improve our recipes)</string>
    <string name="comment_1">NO COMMENT</string>
    <string name="post">Post</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_page_compose">HomePageCompose</string>
    <string name="time_hint"><font size="15">Duration in Minutes</font></string>
    <string name="apiKey">AIzaSyCH9vxYf1w9z7XxsFmaMLy8uJImEikYU_c</string>
</resources>